Let me tell me why.
It all started with the fact that I completely innocently ordered home Air Up.
That flavoring plain water via the scented mind-
-So you experience flavors such as watermelon, pineapple or apple.
The problem now is that the police think that these are too good to be legal.
For everything else that is good in life, usually cost in one way or another.
For example, if you drink alcohol, well then you become backwards.
For example, if you eat useless food, then you feel worse.
But Air Rup has chopped the system.
Only the advantages, though without the disadvantages.
- There he is!!!
Air Up flavors regular tap water with scent.
As the scent mind accounts for 80% of all tastes you experience-
-This your brain interprets the scent of this little pod as a taste.
- We need reinforcement to E4 northbound.
Mauri gets hold of an Air Up bottle.
-And it works so that you fill bottles with water,-
- Oh, I understand!
Woho!
Do you keep up with or?
- Yes, I'm hanging on.
- You have apples.
- Yes, we have many apple trees.
- Can't we run and pallet any apples?
- Shall we do it?
- Yes.
- Should I pallet on my own plot?
- Ah just that.
- Are you involved in a good challenge?
- Yes, in one day.
It's not enough.
- Yes, yes.
- Happy Thursday.
- Look, the bus here in this man.
Now he is in bus mood.
- Yes you drink far too slow guys.
- Are you starting to get a little intoxicated?
You just sit and smile and look out at the horizon.
- I just enjoy the nice summer weather.
- Håkan Fucking Guldkula.
- Cheers, bowl.
- Okay, lunch!
- Lunch!
- I have to thank you so much for being so nice to me.
- Thanks so much for that.
I live on that.
After this, Johan jumped off high school to try out different jobs.
He has been a leisure leader, a store worker, a constitutional porter.
He has run two clothing stores in Örebro, opened a bar in the Old Town.
He has started a floor team in Umeå and he has also trained as a pilot.
And the strangest of all, you have also been a football professional.
In the middle of all this.
Yes, believe it or not, but before Johan's successful business career-
-They he was a brilliant football talent that played in AIK's A-team, among other things.
And he was trained by icon Tommy Söderberg-
Yes.
What do we do now?
How do we celebrate this?
- No, we have to go to Oslo I think to take a sprinkler.
- Cheers!
Bowl!
Then Johan insisted on running Sten Sax's bag for 20,000.
I won, even though I suspect he let me do it with diligence.
And since I am now 10,000 plus again, so you should write what I should do for the money.
Who should I donate them to?
Why?
Write in the comments field.
Then Johan and I went and drove some Norwegian karaoke.
And I could say that although he has absurd a lot of money and in many ways lives in a completely different world than us other-
-So he is in many ways a very ordinary guy and it makes me happy.